Bi-lingual: English and

Multicultural

<u>Gilbenvenitz18@gmail.com</u>

https://www.linkedin.com/in/qil-benvenitz-6b4a501a8

SALES & MARKETING | BUSINESS MANAGEMENT\ FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT

5 Years Combined Multi-Industry Knowledge, Business Development and International Experience

Someone who is constantly motivated, self-driven, and ambitious. Works hard to become one of the knowledgeable people in the group others go to when they're stuck looking for their next step. Enjoys working with groups, but can also appreciate time solving problems alone to gain more of an in-depth understanding. I consider myself someone who has a healthy level of confidence which enables me to have good communication, collaboration, and presentation skills. Diverse knowledge covering multiple fields ranging from Finance, Manufacturing, Full Stack Web Development, Diamonds, and more.

Technical Skills

- -Languages/Libraries/Frameworks:
 - JavaScript | React.js | JQuery | Node.js | Express.js | Bootstrap | Database Theory | MongoDB | SQL | Sequelize | Command Line | HTML5 | CSS3 | Git | Handlebars | Tailwind | Materialize
- Application/Development:
 - VSCode | MySQL Workbench | Insomnia | MongoDB Compass
- -Concepts:

Restful APIs | MVC Model | Variables | Control Structures | Syntax | Data Structures

WORK EXPERIENCE

Belles Gourmet Popcorn

Dallas, TX

2020-2022

Managing Sam's Club (annual account of 4M+)

Inventory Manager/Shipping Coordinator/Account Manager

- Print all Shipping labels through UPS Worldship, and create a filing system to maintain the thousands of active labels we stored
- Constantly monitoring sales and inventory levels in over 250 Sam's Club location nationwide and
 restocking them as necessary. With consideration to rate of sales, production levels, product expiration,
 and remaining time in our Sam's Club shows
- Maintain professional relationships with merchandising companies, merchandising representatives, and lead meetings on how we can improve the show and keep efficient communication between all parties involved. (nearly 250-300 representatives)
- Responsible for a team of 4 individuals on site each with a different role in the chain of fulfillment.
- I have a strong understanding of both google sheets, and excel.

Summary: I can't begin to express my appreciation for the entire team at Belle's popcorn. My time as an inventory manager at Belle's has been one that I'll likely never forget. I have gained a lot of knowledge regarding shipping, customer satisfaction, inventory management, and team leadership qualities.

Nir Diamond Trading

Dallas, TX

2019-2020(6months)

Entrusted with quarter of a million dollars in inventory

Executive Assistant/Sales Rep

- Engaged with customers to effectively build rapport and lasting relationships.
- Prepared cash deposits with zero discrepancies.
- Managed Inventory cost and price setting
- Delivered high level of assistance by locating products and checking store system for merchandise at other sites.
- Family Business

Summary: Definitely a good eye opener into the world falling into the family business, but I learned first hand why it's a bad idea to work with family. Was a great intro into adulting, but I quickly realized I wasn't passionate about the diamond industry and decided to see what else is out there for me.

EDUCATION

UT Austin Bootcamp

Online

March-June 2022

Full Stack Web Development

- Worked on various projects and assignments
- Gained all of the Technical skills listed at the top of the page.

Bachelor of Science: Finance and Financial Management Services

Reichman University (IDC University) - Herzliya - Israel Sep 2016 - August 2019